So the correct answer is while(len &lt; 101).
إذن، الإجابة الصحيحة هي: while(len &lt; 101).
The idea is to repeat this loop
الهدف هو تكرار هذه الحلقة
for as long as len is still not equal to it's correct length.
طالما أن len لا تساوي طولها الصحيح.
So as long as it's still smaller than 101, we add another zero.
لذا، طالما أنها أصغر من 101، سنضيف صفراً آخر.
If we actually added an equal sign here so that
إن أضفنا في الواقع إشارة يساوي "=" هنا
the condition is while(len &lt; or equal to 101),
بحيث تصبح الحالة while(len &lt;= 101)،
that would end up having an extra zero,
سيُضاف صفر آخر في النهاية،
because it would still step into the loop and add that extra digit.
لأنه لا يزال سيدخل إلى الحلقة ويضيف ذلك العدد الإضافي.
If you're still not convinced,
إن لم تكن مقتنعاً بعد،
let's try to trace the last few steps in
لنحاول تتبع آخر بضعة خطوات
that loop and see what's actually happening behind the scenes.
في تلك الحلقة وتفقد ما يحدث فعلاً خلف الكواليس.
So on our string googol has 97 zeroes in it.
في سلسلتنا، تحتوي googol على 97 صفراً.
Our len variable would get updated to 98,
سيتم تحديث متغير len إلى 98،
because that's 1 followed by 97 zeroes,
لأنه 1 يتبعه 97 صفراً
so that's 98 characters.
أي 98 حرفاً.
But still, 98 is less than 101,
لكن لا تزال 98 أقل من 101،
making our while conditions still true.
ما يبقي حالة while هي true.
So we step in again, add another zero,
فندخل مجدداً ونضيف صفراً آخر،
so we have 98 zeroes so far,
فيصبح لدينا 98 صفر حتى الآن،
and our length is 99.
والطول هو 99.
99 is still less than 101, so that's true.
لا تزال 99 أقل من 101، قيمة هذه إذن هي true.
Because it's true, we step in again and we add another zero to it,
ولأنها true، سندخل مجدداً ونضيف صفراً أخر،
making it one followed by 99 zeroes,
ما يجعلها 1 يتبعه 99 صفراً،
and its length is 100.
وطوله 100.
We finished our loop, we go back to our comparison,
أنهينا حلقتنا، ونعود إلى مقارنتنا،
and 100 is less than 101 so it's true.
ولا تزال 100 أقل من 101، فالقيمة هي true.
Now, because it's true,
الآن، بما أنها true،
we step in, we add this extra zero,
سندخل ونضيف صفراً آخر،
so we finally have our googol string having 100 zeroes following the one.
لتصبح أخيراً سلسلة googol فيها 1 يتبعه 100 صفر.
The next step is that we update our len variable,
الخطوة التالية هي تحديث المتغير len،
which makes it 101,
ما يجعل قيمته 101،
and then we reach our end of the loop.
ثم نصل إلى نهاية الحلقة.
We go back up, and because now len is 101,
نعود إلى الأعلى، وبما أن len الآن هي 101،
it's no longer less than 101,
فلم تعد أقل من 101،
which means this condition is actually false.
ما يعني أن هذه الحالة هي false في الحقيقة.
So, we exit the loop with our string having exactly 100 zeroes following that one.
لذا، نخرج من الحلقة وسلسلتنا فيها بالضبط 100 صفر تتبع 1.